(Penny:)Hey, if you're pausing
for dramatic effect,
(Penny:)I'd keep it moving.
(Leonard:)No, no.
(Leonard:)People don't talk
about surface tension.
(Leonard:)If you imagine our
three-space as the surface
(Leonard:)of an N-dimensional
superfluid bubble...
(Leonard:)This... is exciting.
(Leonard:)This is really exciting.
(Leonard:)I have to go
find Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Okay, well,
if you find him,
(Penny:)use the kitchen island--
(Penny:)that coffee table will not
support both of you.
(Leonard:)Which means a spherical
multidimensional superfluid
(Leonard:)shows the same negative-energy
density as space-time.
(Leonard:)So what do you think? What do
you think? So what do you think?
(Sheldon:)Hmm...
(Leonard:)What? Is it wrong?
(Leonard:)Have you seen it somewhere else?
(Sheldon:)Hmm...
(Leonard:)I know this isn't my area,
(Leonard:)and I could never
do the math like you can,
(Leonard:)but could this be something...?
(Leonard:)Well...